Register of the Okhrana records
Hoover Institution Archives
- XXVIII. Miscellaneous (Boxes 217-227, 237-238, 245)
  - Three printers' cuts of unidentified photographs (Index XXVIII, Box 218)
  - Unused stationary of the Russian Embassy in Paris and the M.V.D. (Okhrana) office; official envelopes, one with the seal A.N.; unused scrap paper pad; loose paper (Index XXVIII, Boxes 218, 238)
  - Assortment of medical prescriptions for Chief Krasil'nikov (Index XXVIII, Box 218)
  - Wooden tray for pencils (Index XXVIII, Box 218)
  - Empty portfolio for Russian bank notes (Index XXVIII, Box 219)
  - Four empty folders for filing incoming and outgoing dispatches (Index XXVIII, Box 219)
  - Erasers, tape, thread, items from writing desk drawer (Index XXVIII, Box 220)
  - Collection of calling cards (Index XXVIII, Box 220)
  - Three desk blotters and a ruler (Index XXVIII, Box 220)
  - Miscellaneous papers, pamphlets and publications (Index XXVIII, Boxes 221-225, Map case)
    Includes letters of credit from the Crédit Lyonnais, post card albums, travel guidebooks to various countries and cities, and foreign language grammar books.
  - Assorted maps and city plans of Europe (Index XXVIII, Box 225, Map case)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets (Index XXVIII, Box 225)
  - Panoramic photographs of Switzerland, Russian Red Cross in Stockholm pamphlet, and Monitore Italo-Russo, no. 6, 1917 (Index XXVIII, Box 226)
  - Index cards (Index XXVIII, Box 227)
  - "Source Materials from the Okhrana Archives Pertaining to Political Intervention of the Central Powers in the Russian Revolutionary Movement," by Arsene G. Yourieff, circa 1916 (Box 237)
  - French manuscript on Socialist Revolution, 1908 (Box 238)
  - Annotated piece of wood, undated (Box 238)
  - Shipping crate, undated (Box 245)
- XXIX. Inventories (Box 228)
  - Packing list for the contents of 17 boxes prepared for shipping on August 31, 1920 (Index XXIX, Folder 1)